The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Moving through the meridians like that
consumes too much spiritual energy.
What ?
Master, are you crazy !?
If you drink a Desolate Beast's marrow essence,
you'll explode from the inside !
It's alright, you can explode then.
I don't care !
The first spell Ancient Gods learn
is the Ancient God Tactic.
The Ancient God Clan uses this method
to devour the spiritual energy of all things in the world.
No matter how much there is,
it can all be devoured.
That's the Ancient God Tactic.
Break !
I can't see through this person's cultivation.
But the feeling he gives me
is even more terrifying than a Soul Formation cultivator.
Still running away ?
Stop !
You dare to try to fly
through the meridians with a Core Formation cultivation.
You're quite bold, aren't you ?
Flood Dragon marrow essence...
Senior,
do you recognize this item ?
Back in the first trial,
I subdued a Flood Dragon.
When I was done playing with it,
I killed it for its marrow.
Nothing here can catch my eye.
I'm very disappointed.
The Flood Dragon in the first trial was too weak.
It seems that this is all the Land of the Ancient God
has to offer.
He's the one who left that writing !
Do you dare to consume Flood Dragon marrow essence
because you're a Soul Devourer ?
Yes !
Yes, my ass !
You were about to explode and die !
Is it also because you're a Soul Devourer that you can
move through the Ancient God's meridians ?
Yes.
Bullshit !
It's clearly because of the Ancient God's inheritance !
Come with me to greet Master.
If it weren't for my special authority,
even I wouldn't be able
to move freely within the Ancient God's meridians.
This brat
might be useful.
Duo Mu
pays respects to Master.
Kneel !
You talk too much.
I'm sorry, Master is right.
No spiritual energy fluctuations ?
I didn't even feel his Divine Sense ?
So this is pure
Ancient God power !
You...
Are you a Soul Devourer ?
Yes.
As expected...
Devour it.
Look at it !
A little brat
only took a few breaths
to break the seal that you trash
couldn't break for thousands of years !
In the next 10 years,
those who cannot refine the Divine Sense seal on their bodies
will serve no more purpose.
Inheritor,
you must never let my memory inheritance
fall in Tuo Sen's hands.
Remember... Remember...
The day the demon Tuo Sen breaks free
will be the day
all living beings shall suffer a calamity
But if I refuse to devour the seal,
I'm afraid he'll kill me on the spot.
This Soul Devourer is too young.
Make him condense a Soul Core
or he'll devour too slowly.
This subordinate is willing to lend a hand
to make the Soul Devourer condense a Soul Core.
Go...
Little guy,
when I caught you earlier,
what were you doing in the Dead Soul Sea ?
Senior, you're a Blood Sea Warrior,
why did you bring me to the Nirvana Space of the third trial
where Tuo Sen can't see us ?
Brat,
do you know how long it has been since someone spoke to me like that ?
Junior, you have some nerve.
We aren't really Blood Sea Warriors,
the eleven of us
are foreign cultivators trapped here by Tuo Sen.
In the past 1000 years,
only 3 people escaped.
Once Tuo Sen breaks the seal,
we will all die.
Now,
answer my question.
What were you doing ?
I tried to leave the Land of the Ancient God.
Did you all hear that ?
This little guy
has the same goal as us.
When he breaks Tuo Sen's seal,
it will be our moment to attack.
A Soul Devourer ?
Very good...
Little guy,
once you seal Tuo Sen again,
we will definitely reward you generously.
Senior, you're too kind.
But with my mere Core Formation cultivation,
sealing an Ancient God
is but a dream.
You won't use your cultivation to seal him.
The seal you will devour
is the Ancient God's Divine Sense.
You just need to use your Soul Devourer powers
when Tuo Sen enters the Dead Soul Sea
to trigger the Ancient God's Divine Sense to seal Tuo Sen again.
You can
leave the rest to us.
After we're done,
we will give you 100 top-quality spirit stones.
What ?
Are you not satisfied ?
I'll also give you a top tier artifact,
the Huan Yuan Beast Trap.
Is it enough now ?
Brat,
if you won't cooperate
then we will use another way without a Soul Devourer.
It's not that I don't trust you Seniors
but this is a matter of life or death,
I need a guarantee from you.
What do you want ?
I want your life artifacts.
You !
It's alright.
After all this is done,
Junior will give them back to you.
I'm sure Seniors
wouldn't worry about a Core Formation Junior like me
being able to steal your artifacts for myself, right ?
This is a Soul Core.
Swallow it
and you'll be able to break Tuo Sen's seal.
This day
has finally come...
A Divine Sense barrier ?
Tu Si,
you couldn't beat me 10 000 years ago.
Now
is no different !
I, Tuo Sen,
am back !
Tu Si is dead.
On Tu Si's behalf,
I summon his life artifact.
Star Destroyer Spear,
appear...
I order everyone
to follow me to obtain
the Ancient God's memory inheritance !
Your life artifact, the Star Destroyer Spear
has already submitted to me.
Tu Si,
you cannot stop me !
Passage to the Ancient God's memories...
Appear !
Duo Mu and the others' positions seem random
but in reality they surrounded Tuo Sen.
Are they that confident in dealing with him ?
Little guy,
why aren't you moving ?
Senior doesn't need to be so cautious.
My cultivation is limited
so I'm a little slow.
Senior, I won't delay your plan.
The Soul Core increases a Soul Devourer's power and also strengthens its control over wandering souls. It is generally formed by devouring a huge amount of souls right after becoming a Soul Devourer. Wang Lin didn't form one because he left the Foreign Battlefield too early after becoming a Soul Devourer.
Count the specks of time
floating down gently.
The carving knife in your hands etches out destiny.
Forever lock away the scars
of this mortal life.
This fleeting youth is a thing of the past.
The flying bird could not escape the twilight
that fills the sky with a myriad of colors.
The night-blooming flower cannot drink
the crystalization of the golden wind and the jade dew.
I will ask the heavens who exactly
sliced open this world
to let the rain fall in.
I will refine the world
to make our palm lines say
that we will live forever.
Walking off the beaten path
through heaven and earth.
Before returning to dust,
I will refine this mortal body.
The left shore is the joyous laughter
that can brighten up a thousand years of sadness.
The right shore is an eternal silence
lingering under the candlelight.
To overturn this fate,
I will walk against the heavens.
I will even gather the clouds
to illuminate the sky for you.
All this sadness was not meaningless.
How many lives and deaths\Nhave passed in the blink of an eye ?
I vow to break
this chess game of fate.